Guide to the Richard Marshall Collection of Gay Erotica and Pornography MSS.498
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I. Pulp Novels, 1972-1996, undated; 5 Linear Feet in 5 record cartons.
  - Coxe, Jed. Ride a Hard Cop. San Diego, California. Surrey House, Inc. 1973. MH 407., 1986; cuid23404 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Wynters, Bob. Long Hard Wynters. San Diego, California. Surrey House, Inc. 1973. MH 414., cuid23405 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Glanz, Dick. By the Balls. San Diego, California. Surrey House, Inc. 1973. MH 416., cuid23406 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Wynters, Bob. Wynter's Balls. San Diego, California. Surrey House, Inc. 1973. MH 431., cuid23407 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Griffon, David. Ask Ol' Buddy. San Diego, California. Surrey House, Inc. 1973. MH 432., cuid23408 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Rogers, Tom. Come Free. San Diego, California. Surrey House, Inc. 1974. MH 435., cuid23409 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Kincaid, Jeff. Watersport. San Diego, California. Surrey House, Inc. 1974. MH 447., cuid23410 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Kincaid, Jeff. The Hairy Throne. San Diego, California. Surrey House, Inc. 1974. MOA 118., cuid23411 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Lawrence, Jim. Bikers' Slave. Santee, California. Surrey House, Inc. 1975. SS 001., cuid23412 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Lawrence, Jim. Bikers' Slave. Santee, California. Surrey House, Inc. 1975. SS 001., cuid23413 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Hancock, Bob. Truckin' Suckin', Sailor. Santee, California. Surrey House, Inc. 1975. SS 004, cuid23414 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Series II. Magazines and Serials, 1948-2011, undated; 8 Linear Feet in 8 record cartons.
  This series is organized into two subseries. Both subseries are arranged alphabetically by title and chronologically within:
  Subseries II.A. Magazines, 1948-2011, undated
  Subseries II.B. Serials, 1981-2000
  This series contains mainstream, erotic, and pornographic publications.
  - Subseries II.A. Magazines, 1948-2011, undated; 6.25 Linear Feet in 6 record cartons and 2 flat file folders.
    The magazines were arranged alphabetically by title and chronologically within.
    This subseries contains widely-themed magazines including clothing store quarterlies, fashion, sexual fetishes and interests, as well as pictoral pornographic publications.
    - A&F Quarterly, Ohio, Abercrombie & Fitch, Christmas 1997, Issue 97, cuid23415 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - A&F Quarterly, Ohio, Abercrombie & Fitch, Spring 1998, Issue 98, cuid23416 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - A&F Quarterly, Ohio, Abercrombie & Fitch, Summer 1998, cuid23417 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - A&F Quarterly, Ohio, Abercrombie & Fitch, Fall, 1998; cuid23418 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - A&F Quarterly, Ohio, Abercrombie & Fitch, 2002, Christmas, issue 22, cuid23419 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Abercrombie & Fitch, Maryland, Abercrombie & Fitch, Nov 1998, Christmas, cuid23420 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Abercrombie & Fitch, Maryland, Abercrombie & Fitch, Feb 1999, Spring Break, cuid23421 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Abercrombie &; Fitch, Maryland, Abercrombie & Fitch, April 1999, Summer, cuid23422 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Abercrombie & Fitch, Maryland, Abercrombie & Fitch, July 1999, Back to School, cuid23423 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Abercrombie & Fitch, Maryland, Abercrombie & Fitch, Nov 1999, Christmas, cuid23424 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Abercrombie & Fitch, Maryland, Abercrombie & Fitch, Feb 2000, Spring Break, cuid23425 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Abercrombie & Fitch, Maryland, Abercrombie & Fitch, April 2000, Summer, cuid23426 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Abercrombie & Fitch, Maryland, Abercrombie & Fitch, July 2000, Back to School, cuid23427 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Abercrombie & Fitch, Maryland, Abercrombie & Fitch, July 2001, Back to School, cuid23428 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Abercrombie & Fitch, Maryland, Abercrombie & Fitch, July 2002, Back to School, cuid23429 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Abercrombie & Fitch, Ohio, Abercrombie & Fitch, Nov 2002, Christmas, cuid23430 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - AMG Raw, California, Golden State News, 1979, Issue 1, cuid23431 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Balls, California, Pantheon Productions, 1981, Issue 1, cuid23432 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Bel Ami, New York, Mandate Publications, 1996, v.3 n.3, cuid23433 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Black Sheets, California, Black Boots, 1997, nos.10 and 12, cuid23434 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Brown Hanky Journal, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1986, n.1, cuid23435 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Brown Hanky Journal, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1986, n.1, cuid23436 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Brown Hanky Journal, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1987, n.2, cuid23437 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Brown Hanky Journal, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1987, n.3, cuid23438 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Brown Hanky Journal, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1987, n.4, cuid23439 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Brown Hanky Journal, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1988, n.5, cuid23440 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Brown Hanky Journal - Guard Duty, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1989, n.6, cuid23441 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Brown Hanky Journal - Guard Duty, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1989, n.6, cuid23442 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Brown Hanky Journal, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1990, n.7, cuid23443 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Brown Hanky Journal, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1991, n.8, cuid23444 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Brown Hanky Journal, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1993, n.9, cuid23445 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Brown Hanky Journal, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1995, n.10, cuid23446 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Brown Hanky Journal, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1995, n.11, cuid23447 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Brown Hanky Journal, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1996, n.12, cuid23448 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Brown Hanky Journal, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1997, n.13, cuid23449 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Brown Hanky Journal, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1998, n.14, cuid23450 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Brown Hanky Journal, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1998, n.15, cuid23451 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Brown Hanky Journal - Root 66 Scatman, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 2000, n.16, cuid23452 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Blue Boy's 10 Best Men, Undated; cuid23453 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Brentwood, v.3, Undated; cuid23454 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Brentwood,v.6, Undated; cuid23455 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Buddy, n.132, Undated; cuid23456 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Butt, Amsterdam, Summer 2004, n.10, cuid23457 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Butt, Amsterdam, Spring 2006, n.15, cuid23458 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Butt, Amsterdam, Autumn 2006, n.17, cuid23459 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Butt, Amsterdam, Spring 2007, n.19, cuid23460 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Butt, Amsterdam, Summer 2007, n.20, cuid23461 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Butt, Amsterdam, Autumn/Winter 2007, n.21, cuid23462 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Butt, Amsterdam, Spring 2008, n.22, cuid23463 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Butt, Amsterdam, Winter 2008/9, n.25, 2008-2009; cuid23464 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Butt, Amsterdam, Spring 2009, n.26, cuid23465 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Butt, Amsterdam, Fall 2009, n.27, cuid23466 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Butt, Amsterdam, Spring 2010, n.28, cuid23467 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Calvin Klein Jeans, Calvin Klein, Undated; cuid23468 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Colt: Anniversary Albums, California, Colt Studio, v.4, Undated; cuid23469 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Colt Men, California, Colt Studio, n.3, 1978; cuid23470 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Colt Men, California, Colt Studio, n.8, 1980; cuid23471 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Colt: The Men, The Myth, The Muscles (Collectors edition), California, Colt Studio, Winter, 2004; cuid23472 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Colt Studio Presents, California, Colt Studio, 1986, n.1, cuid23473 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Colt Studio Presents, California, Colt Studio, 1986, n.8, cuid23474 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Colt Studio Presents, California, Colt Studio, 1987, n.9, cuid23475 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Colt Studio Presents, California, Colt Studio, 1987, n.10, cuid23476 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Colt Studio Presents, California, Colt Studio, 1987, n.11, cuid23477 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Colt Studio Presents, California, Colt Studio, 1989, n.12, cuid23478 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Colt Studio Presents, California, Colt Studio, 1998, n.19, cuid23479 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Crisc-oh, California, Incognito Publishing, n.1, Undated; cuid23480 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Cuir, California, The Leather Journal, 1995, Issue 17, cuid23481 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Cum and Get It, California, Academy Press, 1985, v.1 n.1, cuid23482 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Cum Buddies, n.1, Undated; cuid23483 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Drummer, California, Alternate Publishing, 1978, v.3 n.22, cuid23484 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Drummer, California, Alternate Publishing, 1978, v.3 n.25, cuid23485 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Drummer, California, Alternate Publishing, 1978, v.4 n.28, cuid23486 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Drummer, California, Alternate Publishing, 1979, v.4 n.29, cuid23487 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Drummer, California, Alternate Publishing, 1979, v.4 n.31, cuid23488 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Drummer, California, Alternate Publishing, 1979, v.4 n.32, cuid23489 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Drummer, California, Alternate Publishing, 1980, v.4 n.33, cuid23490 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Drummer, California, Alternate Publishing, 1980, v.4 n.35, cuid23491 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Drummer, California, Alternate Publishing, 1980, v.4 n.37, cuid23492 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Drummer, California, Alternate Publishing, 1980, v.5 n.38, cuid23493 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Drummer, California, Alternate Publishing, 1981, v.5 n.46, cuid23494 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Drummer, California, Alternate Publishing, 1981, v.5 n.50, cuid23495 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Drummer, California, Alternate Publishing, 1982, v.6 n.53, cuid23496 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Drummer: The Leather Fraternity Class of '82, California, Alternate Publishing, 1982; cuid23497 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Drummer, v.10, n.87, Undated; cuid23498 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Drummer, California, Desmodus Inc, Oct 1986, v.11 n.99, cuid23499 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Drummer, California, Desmodus Inc, Oct 1987, n.110, cuid23500 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Drummer, California, Desmodus Inc, Mar 1988, n.114, cuid23501 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Drummer, California, Desmodus Inc, July 1988, n.119, cuid23502 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Drummer, California, Desmodus Inc, Aug 1988, n.120, cuid23503 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Drummer, California, Desmodus Inc, May 1990, n.139, cuid23504 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Drummer, California, Desmodus Inc, Nov 1990, n.144, cuid23505 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Drummer, California, Desmodus Inc, May 1991, n.149, cuid23506 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Drummer, California, Desmodus Inc, Oct 1993, n.168, cuid23507 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Drummer, California, Desmodus Inc, July 1994, n.176, cuid23508 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Drummer, California, Desmodus Inc, Aug 1984, n.177, 1994; cuid23509 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Drummer, California, Desmodus Inc, Feb 1995, n.182, cuid23510 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Drummer, California, Desmodus Inc, Sept 1995, n.188, cuid23511 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Drummer, California, Desmodus Inc, Aug 1996, n.198, cuid23512 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Drummer, California, Desmodus Inc, Oct 1996, n.200, cuid23513 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Drummer, California, Desmodus Inc, Jan 1997, n.201, cuid23514 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Drummer, California, Desmodus Inc, Apr 1997, n.203, cuid23515 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Drummer, California, Desmodus Inc, July 1997, n.205, cuid23516 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Drummer, California, Desmodus Inc, Aug 1997, n.207, cuid23517 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Drummer Buddies, California, Desmodus Inc, v.3., n.3, Undated; cuid23518 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Drummer: Hard Core, California, Desmodus Inc, n.1, 1996; cuid23519 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Etienne: The Art of Etienne, Target Studios, 1980; cuid23520 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Etienne: The Erotic Art of Etienne, California, Falcon Studios, n.2, 1984; cuid23521 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Etienne: Storytime 5, Falcon Studios, 1991; cuid23522 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Etienne: Erotica, Book 1, 1999; cuid23523 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Eyemazing magazine, Amsterdam, Issue 4, 2009; cuid25277 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - The Fantastic World of Bill Ward, California, Alternate Publishing, v.3, Undated; cuid23524 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Fizeek Art Quarterly, Washington D.C., Fizeek Enterprises, Fall 1966, n.19, cuid23525 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Fizeek Art Quarterly, Washington D.C., Fizeek Enterprises, Winter 1966, n.20, cuid23526 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Fizeek Art Quarterly, Washington D.C., Fizeek Enterprises, n.22, 1967; cuid23527 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Fizeek Art Quarterly, Washington D.C., Fizeek Enterprises, Spring 1968, n.23, cuid23528 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Folsom, California, Folsom Magazine, n.4, 1981; cuid23529 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Gai Pied Hebdo, n.5, Undated; cuid23530 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Gai Pied Hebdo, Paris, Undated; cuid23531 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Hand Book, California, 2007, v.1 Issue 4, cuid23532 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Hard Ball, Winter, 1984-1985; cuid23533 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Hard Ball, Summer, 1986; cuid23534 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Heavy Load, Issue 2, Undated; cuid23535 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Him, London, Alan Purcell, Issue 2, Undated; cuid23536 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Hombre, California, Seven Seventy, v.1 n.1, Undated; cuid23537 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Honcho, New York, Modernismo Publications Ltd, April 1978, v.1 n.1, cuid23538 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Honcho, New York, Modernismo Publications Ltd, Sept 1978, v.1 n.5, cuid23539 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Honcho, New York, Modernismo Publications Ltd, 27363, v.1 n.8, 1978; cuid23540 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Honcho, New York, Modernismo Publications Ltd, Dec 1978, v.2 n.16, 1979; cuid23541 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Honcho, New York, Modernismo Publications Ltd, Aug 1979, v.2 n.20, cuid23542 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Honcho, New York, Modernismo Publications Ltd, Oct 1980, v.3 n.5, cuid23543 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Honcho, New York, Modernismo Publications Ltd, Feb 1981, v.3 n.8, cuid23544 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Honcho, New York, Modernismo Publications Ltd, Oct 1981, v.4 n.15, cuid23545 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Honcho, New York, Modernismo Publications Ltd, Dec 1981, v.4 n.16, cuid23546 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Honcho, New York, Modernismo Publications Ltd, Feb 1982, v.4 n.19, cuid23547 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Honcho, New York, Modernismo Publications Ltd, Jan 1991, v.14 n.1, cuid23548 (Box 8, Folder 8a)
    - Honcho, New York, Modernismo Publications Ltd, Nov 1992, v.15 n.11, cuid23549 (Box 8, Folder 8a)
    - Honcho, New York, Modernismo Publications Ltd, Feb 1994, v.17 n.2, cuid23550 (Box 8, Folder 8a)
    - Honcho, New York, Modernismo Publications Ltd, April 1994, v.17 n.4, cuid23551 (Box 8, Folder 8a)
    - The Best of Honcho, Undated; cuid23552 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - The Best of Honcho: part two, New York, Modernismo Publications Ltd, 1980; cuid23553 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Illico, Paris, Illico Publications, Dec., 2003; cuid23554 (Box 8, Folder 9a)
    - In Magazine, Paris, June/July 1974, n.11, Undated; cuid23555 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Instigator Magazine, Instigator Magazine, nv.1 issue 5, Undated; cuid23556 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Instigator Magazine, California, Instigator Magazine, v.1 issue 6, Undated; cuid23557 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Instigator Magazine, California, Instigator Magazine, Issue 15, Undated; cuid23558 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - International Nudist Sun: Youth at Play, n.1, Undated; cuid23559 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Issue, New York, Issue Inc, Fall 2003, Issue 7, cuid23560 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Javelin, New York, Target Studios, n.1, 1975; cuid23561 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Javelin, Target Studios, n.3, 1977; cuid23562 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Jock Collectors Edition, New York, G. T. Publishing, v.1 n.2, 1992; cuid23563 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Jocks, California, Jocks Athletics Company, n.1, 1978; cuid23564 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Kaiserin, Luxembourg, Kaiserin, Sept 2009, Issue 3, cuid23565 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Kink, Barcelona, 2009, v.1 Issue 10, cuid23566 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - The Leather Journal, December 2003, Issue 165, cuid23567 (Box 8, Folder 18a)
    - Like It? Lick It!, Undated; cuid23568 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Little Joe, Little Joe Magazine, n.2, 2011; cuid23569 (Box 8, Folder 19a)
    - Luger (Premier Collector's Edition), Undated; cuid23570 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Macho, California, Alternate Publishing, 1980, v.1 n.4, cuid23571 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Macho, California, Alternate Publishing, 1983, v.2 n.6, cuid23572 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Macho, California, Desmodus Inc, Sept 1990, n.21, cuid23573 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Macho, California, Desmodus Inc, July 1993, n.29, cuid23574 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Macho, California, Desmodus Inc, Oct 1993, n.30, cuid23575 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Macho, California, Desmodus Inc, Feb 1994, n.31, cuid23576 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Macho, California, Desmodus Inc, July 1994, n.33, cuid23577 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Macho, California, Brush Creek Media Inc, March 1997, n.35, cuid23578 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Macho, California, Brush Creek Media Inc, July 2000, n.46, cuid23579 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Mandate, New York, Mandate Publications, January 1997, v.21 n.1, cuid23580 (Box 8, Folder 21a)
    - Manifest Reader, California, Alternate Publishing, 1987, Issue 2, cuid23581 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Manifest Reader, California, Alternate Publishing, 1992, Issue 16, cuid23582 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Manifest Reader, California, Alternate Publishing, 1994, Issue 23, cuid23583 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Manifest Reader, California, Alternate Publishing, 1996, Issue 28, cuid23584 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Manifest Reader, California, Alternate Publishing, 1996, Issue 29, cuid23585 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Manifest Reader, California, Alternate Publishing, 1997, Issue 32, cuid23586 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Manifest Reader, California, Alternate Publishing, 1999, Issue 39, cuid23587 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Manhood Rituals, California, Alternate Publishing, n.1, Undated; cuid23588 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Manhood Rituals, California, Alternate Publishing, n.6, Undated; cuid23589 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Manpower, California, Colt Studios, 1974, n.7, cuid23590 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Nous les hommes, Paris, Spring 1973, n.13, cuid23591 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Olympus, California, Colt Studio, v.1 n.5, 1974; cuid23592 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Olympus, California, Colt Studio, Issue 14, Undated; cuid23593 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - On Campus, Falcon Studios, 1976; cuid23594 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - The One-Handed Library Brochure, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1948; cuid23595 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - The One-Handed Reader Series - The Longhorn Drive, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1969; cuid23596 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - The One-Handed Reader Series - A Trucker's Tale, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1974; cuid23597 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - The One-Handed Reader Series - The S & M Brothers, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1981; cuid23598 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - The One-Handed Reader Series - Satan's Nephew, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1987; cuid23599 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - The One-Handed Reader Series: The Confessions of Satan's Nephew, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1990; cuid23600 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - The One-Handed Reader Series: The Secret DIary of Uncle Joe, Florida, D&W Enterprises (Reprinted from 1978), 1993; cuid23601 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - The One-Handed Reader Series - El Toro: The Fugitive Master, Florida, D&W Enterprises, Also Brown Hanky Journal n.3.5, 1990; cuid23602 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - The One-Handed Reader Series - The Return of the Coney Island Knights, Florida, D&W Enterprises, Also Brown Hanky Journal n.8.5, 1993; cuid23603 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - The One-Handed Reader Series - Overtime Parking, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1996; cuid23604 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - The One-Handed Reader Series - The West Side Highway Story, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1995; cuid23605 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - The One-Handed Reader Series - Adventures at Roadside Park, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1997; cuid23606 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - The One-Handed Reader Series - Adventures at Roadside Park, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1997; cuid23607 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - The One-Handed Reader Series - My Adventures at Glory Hole Lodge, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1998; cuid23608 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - The One-Handed Reader Series - Ardmore Station, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1999; cuid23609 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Perry Ellis Advertising Campaign Book, Perry Ellis, Spring, 1998; cuid23610 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Perry Ellis America Advertising Campaign Book. Perry Ellis, Spring, 1998; cuid23611 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Powerplay, California, Brush Creek Media Inc, 1991, v.1 Issue 1, cuid23612 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Powerplay, California, Brush Creek Media Inc, 1992, v.1 issue 3, cuid23613 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Powerplay, California, Brush Creek Media Inc, May 1995, Issue 6, cuid23614 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Powerplay, California, Brush Creek Media Inc, May 1996, Issue 10, cuid23615 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Powerplay, California, Brush Creek Media Inc, Dec 1996, Issue 12, cuid23616 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Project X, Paris, PX Presse, April 1997, n.18, cuid23617 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Project X, Paris, PX Presse, June 1997, n.20, cuid23618 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Project X, Paris, PX Presse, Oct 1998, n.34, cuid23619 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Project X, Paris, PX Presse, Nov/Dec 1998, n.35, cuid23620 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Project X, Paris, PX Presse, Jan 1999, n.36, cuid23621 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Project X, Paris, PX Presse, Feb 1999, n.37, cuid23622 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Project X, Paris, PX Presse, May 1999, n.40, cuid23623 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Project X, Paris, PX Presse, June/July 1999, n.41, cuid23624 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Project X, Paris, PX Presse, Aug 1999, n.42, cuid23625 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Project X, Paris, PX Presse, Sept 1999, n.43, cuid23626 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Project X, Paris, PX Presse, Oct 1999, n.44, cuid23627 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Project X, Paris, PX Presse, Nov 1999, n.45, cuid23628 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Project X, Paris, PX Presse, Dec 1999, n.46, cuid23629 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Project X, Paris, PX Presse, Jan 2000, n.47, cuid23630 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Project X, Paris, PX Presse, Feb 2000, n.48, cuid23631 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Project X, Paris, PX Presse, March 2000, n.49, cuid23632 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Project X, Paris, PX Presse, Apr 2000, n.50, cuid23633 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Project X: Agenda, Paris, PX Presse, April 1999, v.14, cuid23634 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Project X: Agenda, Paris, PX Presse, July/Aug 1999, v.17, cuid23635 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Project X: Agenda, Paris, PX Presse, Nov 1999, v.20, cuid23636 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Project X: Agenda, Paris, PX Presse, Dec 1999, v.21, cuid23637 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Project X: Agenda, Paris, PX Presse, Jan 2000, v.22, cuid23638 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Project X: Agenda, Paris, PX Presse, Feb 2000, v.23, cuid23639 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Project X: Agenda, Paris, PX Presse, March 2000, v.25, cuid23640 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Project X: Agenda, Paris, PX Presse, Apr 2000, v.25, cuid23641 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Project X: Agenda, Paris, PX Presse, May 2000, v.26, cuid23642 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Provocateur, California, Alluvial Publishing, Dec 1995, v.1 issue 2, cuid23643 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Provocateur, California, Alluvial Publishing, Feb 1996, v.1 issue 3, cuid23644 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Provocateur, California, Alluvial Publishing, July 1996, v.2 issue 5, cuid23645 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Provocateur, California, Alluvial Publishing, Oct 1996, v.2 issue 1, cuid23646 (Box 9, Folder 14a)